Hello hello everyone let's see some additional
company first quarter results let's see
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company provides non-life insurance, the
market cap of this company is
60704, it is a last step company, if we
look at the consolidated result of this company then the
company has a net profit of 152 crores last
year from bottom end the company had a
profit of 398 crores, the profit of the company has
decreased by 1962 percent, last year first
quarter tax GPS was 8.74 and this time
UP STF point two has happened, if from Kabir
and see it is running at 225 and the photo6 of this company
is today the share of the company is at 100.4 price, the
profile list company is Mphasis, this company
provides IT services, the market of this company is
looted and it is a next step company, if we
look at the consolidated result of this company then the company has a
profit of 340 crores last year
in the film, the company had a profit of 275 crores, the
profit of the company increased by 20% in last year first
quarter, hence 4600 if  It has been 1630 and
this company 2036 company year 2397 press
two
play list company is Bajaj Holdings and
Investment, the market cap of this company is
14204, this is a last step company, if we
look at the consolidated result of this company, then the
company has made a huge profit from net seven, last year the
company had a profit of 60, the
profit of the company has
increased by almost fifty percent, last year
first quarter GPS was six and this time
IPL 2017 August lid is going on
and the ratio well of this company, today the share of the company is
Schezwan listed company Indian Energy
Exchange, this company is power trading and
consultancy company's market cap is 3000,
this company's consolidated or
company's
profit is net profit of 6304, last date
in the same quarter the company had a profit of 14322, the
profit sharing of the company
is 4986 big, last year first quarter
GPS was 1.41 and this time GPS is 2.10
If you look at the PE ratio of the system, it is
running at twenty and the PI of this company
is 162. Today the share of the company closed at 446. The
board of the company has also recommended the final tweet of the share at 1.5. The
next company is
Hindustan Zinc Company. The
market cap of this company is 10. This is the
consolidated
profit of this company. The company had a profit of more than 100. The
profit of another company has increased by 1946 percent.
Last year's first quarter GP
was 3.2 and this year it is GP4.6. Now if
God sees the setup, then 2013 is going on and the
PE ratio of this company is ATM. Today the share of the company
closed at 100. That's all for today's
video. We will meet again
in the next video. Till then, good night and take
care.